Agent: Now OK.
Caller: John. Really Ferrall terrorist I
am contented is our company to businesses
in the area and was wondering whether you
lose federal service there and then I was
Agent: You know will quickly book.
Caller: obviously
a lot of companies who use Pick books
and went with them up of some kind is
actually less expensive than. If you
did it in half and I was wondering
if you might be able to me with one of our
present of his. Ilk as you there's no
cause and obviously cannot all.
Agent: A crew we have had some issues and
have stock in them all doing something to
them through fed up in the funds and.
Caller: Come on in the area tomorrow
would you leaven a clock or still be
a good be a better time
Agent: The clock would be but
Caller: I have your a drug
a kind of nice hermit and rolled
in single of future that's correct
Agent: yeah it is.
Caller: accidents like you have always
been their commission as it was and if you
know that I am I fear able to send you.
Some information about our company so you
can review it pros to invest in this
Agent: It's wrong to all think
that dream I will not comment
Caller: excellent. Job. Not
to send this to you right now
and I was look for was within
a mile thank you very much and
hopefully we can do business together
Agent: OK. Hopefully
Caller: THANK YOU HAVE AN I think
Agent: yet though.
Caller: good lad.