The.
Put. A lot. Milk. When
you can even argue yet
you know this push to talk of police to
hold. Things like Unlike so rotten running
. Because of the record this is
a test case scenario from the field here
Yeah exactly I read that it's time for
going to have
a whole new world Oh my so so what's
going on I think what's going on
I don't think it's I mean that. I'm so
fuckin hung I would just come back from
lunch with the police here.
And tell me from box.
That I couldn't make it this
time but I think the waiter is
a fine man that we can say Yeah so you get
it I got onto it yeah yeah good man yeah
come along I haven't Yeah we're looking at
you called me up my earlier and gave me
a lady and I had no idea I just went
with it you know he's pretty good yeah
you know I did
a bit of welfare talk back fifty on others
I might just get around already going on
and fifty miles I'll take something then
and you. And and put you bought last week
that he held. After you really look
like yeah absolutely when we put beyond
we got
a pretty good heads up on the desk about
an hour or so we were all on the back
about what we'd seen with him the big Asian
put it sort of structure on and we just
went with it yeah exactly that's all we
can that we sent messages and the Asian
kids and I think it's an honour. And to be
honest so in those you know we just keep
on using that and you know compliance don't
seem to have any idea that we're using
you know. Keep on doing. That my father
enough to make money in this market anyway
so we just have to stick together and do
whatever we can do to keep that little
going along and we all know playing field
around an example and all. Stuff they
take they got no idea what's going on now
and they were inside like exactly I mean
to be honest with you know the central banks
and still think be running around with
a smile and stay there after I've got
the rock to go on here once I think.
You know what you just give me
a call you next time. Now you can you
recount. The reason lower realize
that you can't have the. Only way to play
the game so you know well if it's us
against them isn't it. And you know what
they felt they done online said adding I
mean to be on the line is all work with the
bank yeah you know right now I call it
the margin in the colic after service I
don't know really what they do now but to
be honest I don't think we make
any money now and they talk
a good book you know that's right tight
in the pipeline the prise. You know what
it's like you know what if oh yeah yeah
yeah I've been on the right side I was just
kind of the dark side. I think.
We all of the dark side.
Had
a bad view up and they can we did so pretty
good it's pretty it's not that all this
good could get used to this sort of where
we are and I think the big garden in our
town. You know well. You know now no one
can really hear me you've got one half
a dozen people sitting
around. Yet now look like
a dork happy or confined Well it's.
Not. That we've got everything in
there that they always I think you know
cut it all off then all that and I think
again it was with the. We were.
I think we don't you know I'm not
sure that. I think you've got
a time when you want second. No it's you
know I haven't we haven't I
know you haven't seen it that.
We've only been here that. I can't
remember the last time I spoke for
ten minutes or telephone. BAKLEY right
so when you got home for the weekend
no matter I reckon I don't see that meeting
sorry other like that happening oh yeah
I know you enjoy that feeling for that
and you. Can't get one of the bookies to
thank you have been allowing actually Iraqi
pay that off the deaf and. So on the
other side of things. Yeah exactly I
mean you know they scratch your back you
scratch their. FACE. So the next sound on
this is going to be missing like I mean
the fact. I think about the few
gaps in that one. I think you have
some legal opinions. But if you had
wobbling that it'd be able to be recorded.
At the bar the way we had we had a
few inquiries Smalling for a couple
a couple of public eases want to know what
was going on cable if you see much of
falling on and up and that if you had like
that nobody can anything anything like
that to the options guys
and it's and that had
a few few calls. Well I wanted
to be honest because there's
a guy said he might have
an interest in just shy of
a long and later on but. You know he
would want to know what we saw and to be
honest cable not my strong point I just
made something up as usual but you know
this place I think the centre of the
universe is in the UK so I probably know the
good in fact I'm
a long life yeah exactly have you got
much cooking in the fix for surviving on
there is
a bit around and I've heard that he's
been saying it to Iran it is going to be
sending up quite a bit of a time quite
a bit in the you know I. Suppose some
decent. Which way you could phone way I'll
give you a shout I think it's going
to be on the right hand side I think
a whole lot of if I get some come through
it we normally get ours in the next half
an hour ago come through on the show you
know you can do it you know you some
decent it together with that's right and
just sort of. Didn't up the cost of
service at the end I think well you know
if it works and you know will you can buy
me dinner next time next time I'll do it
and you can buy me and I'll buy you dinner
I feel like I just discovered
a few more names on the go flight back
running will have to come up with small code
words I think is I think these wankers who
are listening to our conversations are
getting used to the. Fact that they
get the new book out scrambled up.
WILL Well we've next time we go out for
a beer we can sort and so on that old
word and I mean and what we were using we
care about what happens to the work of the
granting of the idea that you know that
I fear that ageing out on this mine and I
love you know yeah they do like we turn
that around on the back yeah that's right
and they're happy to sing like canaries
as well yeah yeah I come up
with see where they went
a few things acronyms and yeah that was
like I said I've. Father. Never We won't
know what hit them that. We
were on the market killed.
We still got
a bit of something now here as has the
family have the kids get older and know
it's all down well so miming
moving at home so that I get
a free bit of space for holidays and had
you pop back I think you go on anyway Oh
look I haven't booked anything yet. The
Mrs just flown off to Europe and the kids
have gone as well from it just
mean that or get home yeah
a week or so and they can cry you know I
did some to come up anyway take it so you
know they can you know look I'm planning
to go to Europe at some place I got to go
and see the family or see my parents and
then and. We'll see more of life and I
think it'll put quality around about
September move on. Or just close it down
the the meeting before then and then we'll
just have to be the call lead and away
we go together come back yeah I mean how's
your year going so yeah you know to back
up to that yeah you know. You might budget
so hard been yeah Slowly slowly I think
will come to come across the line anyway I
think I got it back to your place get on
bonuses this girl and I think. They need
to get to come back next year exactly you
know like you know what second thing
is now yes you know once we get.
The pills litanies walking whatever minutes
and you know you don't think it's an
a ten minute mile and I fell
and I think I'd only got
a lot to my wife longer than ten minutes.
Early for that another glass of wine
exactly that's that's what's emitting
a glass of water and I think I might have
to go to the telly I think if I wake up
early when I get home tonight to me in the
togs that no count. From the telly with
a nice bottle of wine unfortunately haven't
read one. Of them all for you know if
you put it in the door was only going to
go away. I was already probably would have
a crack at some red wine. Watch me
play red instead of plain black like
a light. That.
Would want. Reckon we'll well
and it will look. Like you have
a good weekend then they will cancel money
and unless like anything in the six
party my captain and I can add it mostly
on the right but that it's not good we can
see the kids they liked.